Nathan A. Lloyd, LCSW

2923 Chimney Rock Lane Louisville, KY 40220 Cell: (859)533-2089

E-mail: nathanalloyd@gmail.com

Portfolio: Github:

Software Engineer

I am a Highly self-motivated and goal-oriented professional committed to pursuing a long-term career change in the tech industry, specifically as a software developer. I have a decade-long track record demonstrating strong analytical and problem-solving skills, computer proficiency, written and verbal communication skills, and the ability to meet project deadlines under pressure. My desired career is one that allows me to continue learning, creating, and innovating.

Skills and Accomplishments

- ♦ Training in programming languages including C#, Javascript, CSS, and HTML.
- ♦ Computer proficiency as evidenced by helping to troubleshoot errors for a new Electronic Medical Records program at a previous position.
- ♦ Strong communication skills including a history of concise written documentation and the ability to de-escalate conflict.
- Resourcefulness and the ability to problem solve creatively following a decade of experience working in the field of mental health. Experience includes working with severe mental illness and substance abuse, both inpatient and outpatient.
- Flexibility and willingness to quickly adapt to change as needed.
- Passionate about learning new skills as evidenced by my decision to change careers. Lifelong interests include technology, design, and video games.
- ♦ Fluent in French as a second language.

Professional History

Student Code Louisville April 2021 - Present Therapist Renew Recovery October 2020 – March 2021 Therapist The Morton Center April 2019 – October 2020 ♦ Clinician Wellspring November 2016 – April 2019 ♦ Social Service Worker CHFS / DCBS November 2014 – October 2016 ♦ Program Director CRCCC July 2013 – October 2014 ♦ Social Worker Bluegrass.org September 2012 – July 2013

♦ Practicum Student Catholic Charities June 2011 – May 2012
♦ Practicum Student Lexington Police Dept. June 2010 – May 2011

Education

Master of Social Work GPA: 3.81 Asbury University, Wilmore, KY Graduated May 2012

Code Louisville

Classes taken: Front End Development, C# Scheduled to graduate November 2021